<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Year 2079</string>
    <string name="governor_context"><![CDATA[You are the governor of Singapore, a major smart city that has consistently been the frontrunner of technological advancements over the years.Many governors before you have faced numerous problems with regards to the city, and have all dealt with them successfully. There is a gratuitous change in global climate pattern in recent years and the change is predicted to be irreversible. As a result, the yield of agriculture all over the world had dropped drastically. All the countries have decreased their export of food to Singapore to ensure the supply of food within their own countries. As the majority of food in Singapore is imported, we are facing the biggest ever problem right now - an imminent severe food shortage. The head of the National Research and Development (NR&D), Doctor Joey Richie L Tan has suggested that the concept of ‘Super Nature Light (SNL)’ could be incorporated in the agriculture. SNL is a newly discovered light with intensity and energy 10 times higher than the natural light we are currently receiving. Shining SNL on plants will provide enough nutrition for the plants and increase the crop yield. Despite being an urgent matter to tackle, there are potential problems associated with the use of super nature light.]]></string>
    <string name="storysetting">The year is 2079, Singapore has evolved into a digitally advanced city, especially with developments of autonomous androids, and technologies that leverage sustainable energy and ergonomic architectural design, it has paved the path of success for the nation. The developed city is now suspended on structures that are connected securely and directly to the seabed. The buildings are shaped to maximise living spaces and to harvest wind energy to power the city. Solar panels are also invested to supplement the growing energy demands of a growing populace. In this story, the following three roles have a major role to play in the management of the city. Given their positions and influence revolving around their job scopes, they have the capacity to make significant decisions that will drastically affect the direction of the country.\n\nGovernor: Has political influence, and can affect constitutional policies and laws \n\nScientist: Innovation of products/inventions in a bid to improve the standard of living \n\nSuperIntelligent Android: Citizens of the city, and they assist humans in making more informed decisions and correcting anomalies. \n\n(Feel free to try out all different roles and see where each path will lead you)</string>

</resources>
